{
	"description": "Vocabulary encountered in erotica",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "１８禁", "answers": [ "じゅうはちきん" ], "comment": "18 certificate; R-18; restricted to those 18 years or older​" },
	{ "question": "３Ｐ", "answers": [ "さんピー" ], "comment": "threesome" },
	{ "question": "４８手", "answers": [ "シジュウハッテ" ] },
	{ "question": "６９", "answers": [ "シックスナイン" ] },
	{ "question": "Ｇスポット", "answers": [ "ジースポット" ], "comment": "G-spot; Grafenberg spot​" },
	{ "question": "Ｍ字開脚", "answers": [ "エムジカイキャク" ], "comment": "pornographic pose (spreading one's legs open wide with knees bent, creating the shape of the letter 'M')​" },
	{ "question": "ＮＧ", "answers": [ "エヌジー" ], "comment": "NG; no good\\ngaffe or \"blooper\" in TV or movies​" },
	{ "question": "Ｒ１８", "answers": [ "アールじゅうはち" ] },
	{ "question": "ＳＭ", "answers": [ "エスエム" ], "comment": "SM; S&M; sado-masochism​" },
	{ "question": "〆込み千鳥", "answers": [ "しめこみちどり" ] },
	{ "question": "〆込み錦", "answers": [ "しめこみにしき" ] },
	{ "question": "お尻", "answers": [ "おしり" ], "comment": "bottom; buttocks" },
	{ "question": "お掃除フェラ", "answers": [ "おそうじフェラ" ] },
	{ "question": "お風呂", "answers": [ "オフロ" ], "comment": "bath" },
	{ "question": "くぐり椅子", "answers": [ "くぐりいす" ] },
	{ "question": "こたつ隠れ", "answers": [ "こたつがくれ" ] },
	{ "question": "さかさ椋鳥", "answers": [ "さかさむくどり" ] },
	{ "question": "させ子", "answers": [ "サセコ" ], "comment": "whore" },
	{ "question": "しめ小股", "answers": [ "しめこまた" ] },
	{ "question": "つぶし駒掛け", "answers": [ "つぶしこまがけ" ] },
	{ "question": "まんぐり返し", "answers": [ "まんぐりがえし" ] },
	{ "question": "アダルト撮影会", "answers": [ "あだるとさつえいかい" ] },
	{ "question": "アナル舐め", "answers": [ "あなるなめ" ], "comment": "anilingus; analingus; rimming; rimjob" },
	{ "question": "オッパイ星人", "answers": [ "オッパイセイジン" ] },
	{ "question": "カウパー腺液", "answers": [ "かうぱーせんえき" ], "comment": "Cowper's fluid; pre-ejaculate; pre-cum" },
	{ "question": "カズノコ天井", "answers": [ "かずのこてんじょう" ] },
	{ "question": "カリ首", "answers": [ "カリクビ" ], "comment": "(something resembling a) goose's neck\nglans; head of a penis" },
	{ "question": "カリ高", "answers": [ "カリダカ" ] },
	{ "question": "ガマン汁", "answers": [ "がまんじる" ], "comment": "pre-ejaculate; pre-ejaculatory fluid; Cowper's fluid; pre-cum" },
	{ "question": "デブ専", "answers": [ "デブセン" ], "comment": "chubby-chasing (fat fetishism); chubby-chaser" },
	{ "question": "トルコ風呂", "answers": [ "トルコぶろ" ], "comment": "Turkish bath\nsoapland (brothel where one can bathe with the prostitutes)" },
	{ "question": "ハメ撮り", "answers": [ "ハメどり" ], "comment": "photographing or filming of sex" },
	{ "question": "パイ刷り", "answers": [ "ぱいずり" ], "comment": "breast fucking; titty fuck" },
	{ "question": "パンスト破り", "answers": [ "ぱんすとやぶり" ] },
	{ "question": "ピストン運動", "answers": [ "ピストンうんどう" ] },
	{ "question": "ワカメ酒", "answers": [ "わかめざけ" ] },
	{ "question": "一夫多妻制", "answers": [ "いっぷたさいせい" ], "comment": "polygamy" },
	{ "question": "一物", "answers": [ "いちもつ" ], "comment": "plot; ulterior motive; secret intention\nthing; article\npenis" },
	{ "question": "一見さん", "answers": [ "いちげんさん" ], "comment": "first-time customer (of an inn or a restaurant); chance customer; customer without an introduction from a regular customer" },
	{ "question": "丁字引き", "answers": [ "ちょうじびき" ] },
	{ "question": "三輪車", "answers": [ "サンリンシャ" ], "comment": "three wheeled vehicle (tricycle, motorcycle, etc.); three wheeler" },
	{ "question": "上がり部屋", "answers": [ "あがりべや" ] },
	{ "question": "上付き", "answers": [ "ウワツキ" ] },
	{ "question": "上反り", "answers": [ "ウワゾリ" ] },
	{ "question": "下り藤", "answers": [ "くだりふじ" ] },
	{ "question": "下着", "answers": [ "したぎ" ], "comment": "underwear" },
	{ "question": "下腹部", "answers": [ "かふくぶ" ], "comment": "abdomen" },
	{ "question": "不妊", "answers": [ "ふにん" ], "comment": "infertility; sterility; barrenness" },
	{ "question": "中絶", "answers": [ "ちゅうぜつ" ], "comment": "abortion\nto be interrupted; to be discontinued; to be suspended; to fall into abeyance" },
	{ "question": "乙女", "answers": [ "おとめ" ], "comment": "little girl; maiden; young lady; female usually between 7 and 18 years old" },
	{ "question": "乱れ牡丹", "answers": [ "みだれぼたん" ] },
	{ "question": "乱交", "answers": [ "ランコウ" ], "comment": "promiscuity; group sex" },
	{ "question": "乳房", "answers": [ "ちぶさ" ], "comment": "breast; nipple; udder" },
	{ "question": "乳頭", "answers": [ "にゅうとう" ], "comment": "(mammary) nipple; teat" },
	{ "question": "乳首", "answers": [ "ちくび" ], "comment": "nipple; teat" },
	{ "question": "亀甲縛り", "answers": [ "きっこうしばり" ], "comment": "tortoise shell bondage; turtle shell bondage" },
	{ "question": "亀頭", "answers": [ "きとう" ], "comment": "glans (esp. glans penis)" },
	{ "question": "交わる", "answers": [ "まじわる" ], "comment": "to cross; to intersect; to join; to meet\nto associate with; to mingle with; to consort with\nto have a sexual relationship; to copulate" },
	{ "question": "交尾", "answers": [ "こうび" ], "comment": "copulation (in animals)" },
	{ "question": "交差位", "answers": [ "こうさい" ] },
	{ "question": "交接", "answers": [ "こうせつ" ], "comment": "sexual intercourse" },
	{ "question": "享楽", "answers": [ "きょうらく" ], "comment": "enjoyment; pleasure" },
	{ "question": "人妻", "answers": [ "ヒトヅマ" ], "comment": "married woman\nanother's wife" },
	{ "question": "仏壇返し", "answers": [ "ぶつだんがえし" ] },
	{ "question": "仰向け", "answers": [ "あおむけ" ], "comment": "face up" },
	{ "question": "会員制", "answers": [ "カイインセイ" ], "comment": "membership system" },
	{ "question": "伸長位", "answers": [ "しんちょうい" ] },
	{ "question": "体臭", "answers": [ "たいしゅう" ], "comment": "body odor; body odour; personal odor; personal odour; characteristic (of someone)" },
	{ "question": "俵抱き本手", "answers": [ "たわらだきほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "側位", "answers": [ "そくい" ], "comment": "lateral sexual position; spoons; spooning" },
	{ "question": "側室", "answers": [ "そくしつ" ], "comment": "concubine (of a noble)" },
	{ "question": "偽乳", "answers": [ "ぎにゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "傾城町", "answers": [ "けいせいまち" ] },
	{ "question": "元気汁", "answers": [ "ゲンキジル" ] },
	{ "question": "充血", "answers": [ "じゅうけつ" ], "comment": "congestion (with blood); hyperemia; hyperaemia" },
	{ "question": "先っちょ", "answers": [ "サキッチョ" ], "comment": "end; tip; point" },
	{ "question": "先細", "answers": [ "サキボソ" ], "comment": "tapering toward the end" },
	{ "question": "先走り汁", "answers": [ "サキバシリジル" ], "comment": "pre-cum; pre-ejaculate; Cowper's fluid" },
	{ "question": "兜合わせ", "answers": [ "かぶとあわせ" ] },
	{ "question": "入浴料", "answers": [ "にゅうよくりょう" ] },
	{ "question": "入船本手", "answers": [ "いりふねほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "全裸", "answers": [ "ぜんら" ], "comment": "nude" },
	{ "question": "八つ橋", "answers": [ "やつはし" ], "comment": "type of sweet made with bean paste (local delicacy in Kyoto); cinnamon-seasoned cracknel (cookie)\nzigzag bridge" },
	{ "question": "八重椿", "answers": [ "やえつばき" ] },
	{ "question": "公衆便所", "answers": [ "こうしゅうべんじょ" ], "comment": "public lavatory\nslut; whore; floozy; tramp; trollop" },
	{ "question": "冷感症", "answers": [ "れいかんしょう" ], "comment": "female sexual arousal disorder; FSAD; anaphrodisia; hyphedonia; frigidity" },
	{ "question": "凌辱", "answers": [ "りょうじょく" ], "comment": "insult; affront; disgrace; indignity\nsexual assault; rape" },
	{ "question": "処女", "answers": [ "しょじょ" ], "comment": "virgin; maiden" },
	{ "question": "処女喪失", "answers": [ "しょじょそうしつ" ], "comment": "loss of virginity (in women); loss of maidenhead" },
	{ "question": "処女膜", "answers": [ "しょじょまく" ], "comment": "hymen\nhymenal (medical, biol.)\nhymeno- (medical, biol.)" },
	{ "question": "出産", "answers": [ "しゅっさん" ], "comment": "childbirth; (giving) birth; delivery; parturition; confinement\nproduction (of goods)" },
	{ "question": "出禁", "answers": [ "デキン" ], "comment": "banishment; being forbidden to enter" },
	{ "question": "出船後ろ取り", "answers": [ "でふねうしろどり" ] },
	{ "question": "分娩", "answers": [ "ぶんべん" ], "comment": "childbirth; delivery; confinement" },
	{ "question": "分泌", "answers": [ "ぶんぴ" ], "comment": "secretion" },
	{ "question": "初体験", "answers": [ "はつたいけん" ], "comment": "first experience (of any activity)\nfirst sexual experience" },
	{ "question": "初夜権", "answers": [ "しょやけん" ], "comment": "right of first night; jus primae noctis; droit du seigneur" },
	{ "question": "刺激", "answers": [ "しげき" ], "comment": "stimulus; impetus; incentive; encouragement; motivation; provocation; excitement; thrill" },
	{ "question": "剃毛", "answers": [ "ていもう" ], "comment": "shaving" },
	{ "question": "前戯", "answers": [ "ぜんぎ" ], "comment": "(sexual) foreplay" },
	{ "question": "割れ目", "answers": [ "われめ" ], "comment": "chasm; interstice; crevice; crack; cleft; split; rift; fissure\nvulva; slit; cunt; vagina; twat" },
	{ "question": "割チケ", "answers": [ "わりちけ" ] },
	{ "question": "割礼", "answers": [ "かつれい" ], "comment": "circumcision (male)" },
	{ "question": "勃起", "answers": [ "ぼっき" ], "comment": "erection (usu. penis); standing erect; stiffening" },
	{ "question": "勃起不全", "answers": [ "ぼっきふぜん" ], "comment": "erectile dysfunction" },
	{ "question": "包皮", "answers": [ "ほうひ" ], "comment": "foreskin; prepuce" },
	{ "question": "千摺り", "answers": [ "せんずり" ], "comment": "masturbation (male)" },
	{ "question": "千鳥の曲", "answers": [ "ちどりのきょく" ] },
	{ "question": "卍崩し", "answers": [ "まんじくずし" ] },
	{ "question": "卑猥", "answers": [ "ひわい" ], "comment": "indecent; obscene" },
	{ "question": "即尺", "answers": [ "ソクシャク" ] },
	{ "question": "卵巣", "answers": [ "らんそう" ], "comment": "ovary" },
	{ "question": "卵細胞", "answers": [ "らんさいぼう" ], "comment": "ovum; egg cell" },
	{ "question": "卵胞", "answers": [ "らんほう" ], "comment": "(ovarian) follicle" },
	{ "question": "受精", "answers": [ "じゅせい" ], "comment": "fertilization; fertilisation; impregnation; pollination" },
	{ "question": "受精卵", "answers": [ "じゅせいらん" ], "comment": "fertilized eggs; fertilised eggs" },
	{ "question": "口付け", "answers": [ "くちづけ" ], "comment": "kiss" },
	{ "question": "口淫", "answers": [ "こういん" ], "comment": "oral sex; fellatio; cunnilingus" },
	{ "question": "口腔内射精", "answers": [ "こうこうないしゃせい" ] },
	{ "question": "口開け", "answers": [ "くちあけ" ], "comment": "opening (of a bottle); broaching\nbeginning; opening; commencement (e.g. of sales); first sale" },
	{ "question": "合意", "answers": [ "ごうい" ], "comment": "agreement; consent; mutual understanding; accord; consensus" },
	{ "question": "吉原", "answers": [ "ヨシワラ" ] },
	{ "question": "同伴出勤", "answers": [ "どうはんしゅっきん" ], "comment": "(a bar hostess) coming to work accompanied by a customer" },
	{ "question": "同性愛", "answers": [ "どうせいあい" ], "comment": "homosexual love" },
	{ "question": "同衾", "answers": [ "どうきん" ], "comment": "sleeping together; sleeping with; sharing a bed" },
	{ "question": "和姦", "answers": [ "わかん" ], "comment": "(consensual) sexual intercourse" },
	{ "question": "唐竹割", "answers": [ "からたけわり" ] },
	{ "question": "唐草居茶臼", "answers": [ "からくさちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "唾", "answers": [ "つば" ], "comment": "saliva; spit; sputum" },
	{ "question": "唾液", "answers": [ "だえき" ], "comment": "saliva; sputum" },
	{ "question": "善がる", "answers": [ "よがる" ], "comment": "to satisfy oneself; to feel satisfied; to be proud" },
	{ "question": "喉射", "answers": [ "のどしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "喘ぎ声", "answers": [ "あえぎごえ" ], "comment": "heavy breathing" },
	{ "question": "嚥下", "answers": [ "えんげ" ], "comment": "(act of) swallowing; deglutition" },
	{ "question": "土手", "answers": [ "どて" ], "comment": "embankment; bank\nbeef sinew stewed in miso and mirin" },
	{ "question": "地雷女", "answers": [ "ジライオンナ" ] },
	{ "question": "坐薬", "answers": [ "ざやく" ], "comment": "suppository" },
	{ "question": "売春婦", "answers": [ "ばいしゅんふ" ], "comment": "prostitute" },
	{ "question": "壺洗い", "answers": [ "ツボアライ" ], "comment": "individually \"washing\" a partner's fingers or toes in one's vagina (esp. as a service at a soapland)" },
	{ "question": "変態プレイ", "answers": [ "へんたいプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "変態性欲", "answers": [ "へんたいせいよく" ], "comment": "abnormal sexuality; sexual perversion" },
	{ "question": "外出し", "answers": [ "ソトダシ" ], "comment": "extravaginal ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "外陰部", "answers": [ "がいいんぶ" ], "comment": "pudenda; external genitalia" },
	{ "question": "夜伽", "answers": [ "よとぎ" ], "comment": "attending someone through the night (guard, nurse)\nact of a woman sleeping with a man (at his bidding)\nkeeping overnight vigil over body before burial" },
	{ "question": "夜這い", "answers": [ "よばい" ], "comment": "creeping at night into a woman's bedroom; stealing into a girl's bedroom at night to make love; sneaking visit" },
	{ "question": "夢精", "answers": [ "むせい" ], "comment": "wet dream; nocturnal emission" },
	{ "question": "大陰唇", "answers": [ "だいいんしん" ], "comment": "labia majora" },
	{ "question": "失禁", "answers": [ "しっきん" ], "comment": "incontinence" },
	{ "question": "奉仕", "answers": [ "ほうし" ], "comment": "service; ministry; attendance; church work\noffering goods at a reduced price; providing a service for free" },
	{ "question": "女体盛り", "answers": [ "ニョタイモリ" ], "comment": "practice of eating sushi or sashimi off an unclad woman's body" },
	{ "question": "女性器", "answers": [ "じょせいき" ], "comment": "female genitalia" },
	{ "question": "女王様", "answers": [ "ジョオウサマ" ] },
	{ "question": "女衒", "answers": [ "ぜげん" ], "comment": "someone who makes their living selling women into prostitution; pimp; procurer" },
	{ "question": "女郎", "answers": [ "じょろう" ], "comment": "prostitute (esp. Edo period)\nbitch" },
	{ "question": "女陰", "answers": [ "にょいん" ], "comment": "female genitals; vulva" },
	{ "question": "妄想", "answers": [ "もうそう" ], "comment": "wild idea; delusion" },
	{ "question": "妊娠", "answers": [ "にんしん" ], "comment": "conception; pregnancy" },
	{ "question": "妊婦プレイ", "answers": [ "ニンププレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "妾", "answers": [ "めかけ" ], "comment": "I; me\nmistress; kept woman; concubine" },
	{ "question": "姉妹丼", "answers": [ "しまいどん" ] },
	{ "question": "姦淫", "answers": [ "かんいん" ], "comment": "adultery; fornication; illicit intercourse" },
	{ "question": "姫始め", "answers": [ "ひめはじめ" ], "comment": "eating the first meal of soft rice (himeii) after the traditional hard rice of New Year (kowaii)\nfirst intercourse of the New Year\nloss of virginity; loss of maidenhead" },
	{ "question": "姫納め", "answers": [ "ヒメオサメ" ] },
	{ "question": "娼婦", "answers": [ "しょうふ" ], "comment": "prostitute; harlot" },
	{ "question": "婚前交渉", "answers": [ "こんぜんこうしょう" ], "comment": "premarital sexual relations (intercourse)" },
	{ "question": "媚薬", "answers": [ "びやく" ], "comment": "aphrodisiac\nlove potion; philter" },
	{ "question": "嫡妻", "answers": [ "ちゃくさい" ], "comment": "one's legal wife; legitimate wife" },
	{ "question": "嬌声", "answers": [ "きょうせい" ], "comment": "coquettish voice; flirtatious voice" },
	{ "question": "子作り", "answers": [ "こづくり" ], "comment": "having children\nattempting to conceive" },
	{ "question": "子宮", "answers": [ "しきゅう" ], "comment": "womb; uterus" },
	{ "question": "子袋", "answers": [ "こぶくろ" ], "comment": "womb; uterus\npork or beef uterus, eaten grilled or raw" },
	{ "question": "宝船", "answers": [ "たからぶね" ], "comment": "treasure ship\npicture of a treasure ship bearing the Seven Gods of Good Fortune" },
	{ "question": "寸止め", "answers": [ "スンドメ" ], "comment": "stopping just before" },
	{ "question": "寿本手", "answers": [ "ことぶきほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "射精", "answers": [ "しゃせい" ], "comment": "ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "射精管理", "answers": [ "しゃせいかんり" ] },
	{ "question": "小陰唇", "answers": [ "しょういんしん" ], "comment": "labia minora" },
	{ "question": "少子化", "answers": [ "しょうしか" ], "comment": "declining birth rates; decrease in the number of children" },
	{ "question": "尺る", "answers": [ "シャクル" ] },
	{ "question": "尺八", "answers": [ "シャクハチ" ], "comment": "shakuhachi; end-blown fippleless bamboo flute\nblow job; fellatio" },
	{ "question": "尻軽", "answers": [ "しりがる" ], "comment": "agility; fickleness; frivolous; of loose morals" },
	{ "question": "尿道", "answers": [ "にょうどう" ], "comment": "urethra" },
	{ "question": "局部", "answers": [ "きょくぶ" ], "comment": "part; section\naffected region\ngenitals; private parts" },
	{ "question": "屈曲位", "answers": [ "くっきょくい" ] },
	{ "question": "屈脚位", "answers": [ "くっきゃくい" ] },
	{ "question": "屍姦", "answers": [ "しかん" ], "comment": "necrophilia; necrophilism" },
	{ "question": "岡場所", "answers": [ "おかばしょ" ], "comment": "red-light district" },
	{ "question": "岩清水", "answers": [ "いわしみず" ], "comment": "water trickling from rocks" },
	{ "question": "巨乳", "answers": [ "きょにゅう" ], "comment": "huge breasts" },
	{ "question": "巨根", "answers": [ "きょこん" ], "comment": "large penis" },
	{ "question": "帆かけ茶臼", "answers": [ "ほかけちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "帝王切開", "answers": [ "ていおうせっかい" ], "comment": "Caesarean section (Cesarean); C-section" },
	{ "question": "帽子", "answers": [ "ボウシ" ], "comment": "hat; cap" },
	{ "question": "年齢制限", "answers": [ "ねんれいせいげん" ], "comment": "age limit; age limits" },
	{ "question": "幼女", "answers": [ "ようじょ" ], "comment": "little girl" },
	{ "question": "床上手", "answers": [ "とこじょうず" ], "comment": "being good in bed; sexual performer" },
	{ "question": "座位", "answers": [ "ざい" ], "comment": "sitting position" },
	{ "question": "座禅転がし", "answers": [ "ざぜんころがし" ] },
	{ "question": "廓", "answers": [ "くるわ" ], "comment": "district; quarter\nenclosure; area enclosed by earthwork\nred-light district\nwide and empty" },
	{ "question": "廓つなぎ", "answers": [ "くるわつなぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "張形", "answers": [ "はりかた" ], "comment": "penis-shaped device, traditionally made of horn, shell or papier mache; dildo" },
	{ "question": "強姦", "answers": [ "ごうかん" ], "comment": "rape; sexual assault" },
	{ "question": "当たり", "answers": [ "あたり" ], "comment": "hit\nsuccess\nguess; prediction\naffability; friendliness\nsensation; touch\nbruise (on fruit)\nsituation in which a stone or chain of stones may be captured on the next move (in the game of go)\nbite (of a fish on a hook); strike\nper; each" },
	{ "question": "後戯", "answers": [ "こうぎ" ], "comment": "postcoital activity; afterplay; pillow talk" },
	{ "question": "後櫓", "answers": [ "うしろやぐら" ] },
	{ "question": "後背位", "answers": [ "こうはいい" ], "comment": "rear entry position (sexual position)" },
	{ "question": "御所車", "answers": [ "ごしょぐるま" ], "comment": "an ox-drawn coach" },
	{ "question": "微乳", "answers": [ "びにゅう" ], "comment": "small breasts; delicate breasts" },
	{ "question": "忍び居茶臼", "answers": [ "しのびちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "快感", "answers": [ "かいかん" ], "comment": "pleasant feeling" },
	{ "question": "快楽", "answers": [ "かいらく" ], "comment": "pleasure" },
	{ "question": "思春期", "answers": [ "ししゅんき" ], "comment": "puberty" },
	{ "question": "性交体位", "answers": [ "せいこうたいい" ], "comment": "sex position" },
	{ "question": "性具", "answers": [ "せいぐ" ], "comment": "sex toy; sex aid" },
	{ "question": "性感帯", "answers": [ "せいかんたい" ], "comment": "erogenous zone" },
	{ "question": "性感染症", "answers": [ "せいかんせんしょう" ], "comment": "sexually transmitted disease; sexually transmitted infection; STD; STI" },
	{ "question": "性技", "answers": [ "せいぎ" ], "comment": "sexual techniques" },
	{ "question": "性欲", "answers": [ "せいよく" ], "comment": "sexual desire" },
	{ "question": "性毛", "answers": [ "せいもう" ] },
	{ "question": "性癖", "answers": [ "せいへき" ], "comment": "disposition; inclination; characteristic; idiosyncrasy; propensity\nsexual disposition; fetish" },
	{ "question": "性的同意年齢", "answers": [ "せいてきどういねんれい" ] },
	{ "question": "性的嗜好", "answers": [ "せいてきしこう" ], "comment": "sexual preference; sexual predilection" },
	{ "question": "性的指向", "answers": [ "せいてきしこう" ], "comment": "sexual orientation" },
	{ "question": "性的興奮", "answers": [ "せいてきこうふん" ], "comment": "sexual arousal; sexual excitation" },
	{ "question": "性行為", "answers": [ "せいこうい" ], "comment": "sex act; intercourse" },
	{ "question": "恋敵", "answers": [ "こいがたき" ], "comment": "one's rival in love" },
	{ "question": "恍惚状態", "answers": [ "こうこつじょうたい" ], "comment": "state of ecstasy (rapture); trance; senile dementia" },
	{ "question": "恥丘", "answers": [ "ちきゅう" ], "comment": "mons pubis; mons veneris" },
	{ "question": "恥垢", "answers": [ "ちこう" ], "comment": "smegma" },
	{ "question": "恥骨", "answers": [ "ちこつ" ], "comment": "pubis; pubes" },
	{ "question": "悪阻", "answers": [ "つわり" ], "comment": "morning sickness; hyperemesis gravidarum" },
	{ "question": "愛し合う", "answers": [ "あいしあう" ], "comment": "to love one another; to be affectionate towards each other\nto have sex; to make love" },
	{ "question": "愛人", "answers": [ "あいじん" ], "comment": "lover; mistress" },
	{ "question": "愛情表現", "answers": [ "あいじょうひょうげん" ], "comment": "expression of love; showing love" },
	{ "question": "愛撫", "answers": [ "あいぶ" ], "comment": "caressing; loving dearly" },
	{ "question": "愛液", "answers": [ "あいえき" ], "comment": "genital secretions; sexual fluids\nsemen; cum" },
	{ "question": "手コキ", "answers": [ "てこき" ], "comment": "hand job" },
	{ "question": "手マン", "answers": [ "てマン" ], "comment": "finger-banging (manual stimulation of female genital organs)" },
	{ "question": "手淫", "answers": [ "しゅいん" ], "comment": "masturbation; onanism" },
	{ "question": "手込め", "answers": [ "てごめ" ], "comment": "rape" },
	{ "question": "手錠", "answers": [ "てじょう" ], "comment": "handcuffs; manacles" },
	{ "question": "抜く", "answers": [ "ぬく" ], "comment": "to extract; to omit; to draw out; to unplug\nto do something to the end\nto surpass; to overtake\nto masturbate (of a male); to ejaculate (while masturbating)\nto take (a photo); to record (video)" },
	{ "question": "抱き地蔵", "answers": [ "だきじぞう" ] },
	{ "question": "押し車", "answers": [ "おしぐるま" ] },
	{ "question": "拘束プレイ", "answers": [ "コウソクプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "括約筋", "answers": [ "かつやくきん" ], "comment": "sphincter; sphincter muscle; constrictor" },
	{ "question": "指入れ", "answers": [ "ゆびいれ" ] },
	{ "question": "指名", "answers": [ "シメイ" ], "comment": "name; nominate; designate" },
	{ "question": "挿入", "answers": [ "そうにゅう" ], "comment": "insertion; incorporation; infixing" },
	{ "question": "排便", "answers": [ "はいべん" ], "comment": "defecation" },
	{ "question": "排卵", "answers": [ "はいらん" ], "comment": "ovulation" },
	{ "question": "排尿", "answers": [ "はいにょう" ], "comment": "urination; micturition" },
	{ "question": "排泄", "answers": [ "はいせつ" ], "comment": "excretion" },
	{ "question": "接吻", "answers": [ "せっぷん" ], "comment": "kiss; kissing" },
	{ "question": "揚羽本手", "answers": [ "あげはほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "撞木ぞり", "answers": [ "しゅもくぞり" ] },
	{ "question": "放尿", "answers": [ "ほうにょう" ], "comment": "urination" },
	{ "question": "放心状態", "answers": [ "ほうしんじょうたい" ], "comment": "being in abstraction; being dazed; being absentminded; stargazing" },
	{ "question": "放置プレイ", "answers": [ "ほうちプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "数の子天井", "answers": [ "カズノコテンジョウ" ] },
	{ "question": "敷き小股", "answers": [ "しきこまた" ] },
	{ "question": "新人", "answers": [ "シンジン" ], "comment": "new face; newcomer; rookie; fresh recruit\nmodern humans (from Cro-Magnon man onwards)" },
	{ "question": "早漏", "answers": [ "そうろう" ], "comment": "premature ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "昇天", "answers": [ "しょうてん" ], "comment": "death; the Ascension" },
	{ "question": "春画", "answers": [ "シュンガ" ], "comment": "shunga; erotic or pornographic woodblock prints" },
	{ "question": "時雨茶臼", "answers": [ "しぐれちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "月経", "answers": [ "げっけい" ], "comment": "menstruation; menstrual period" },
	{ "question": "月見茶臼", "answers": [ "つきみちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "朝立ち", "answers": [ "あさだち" ], "comment": "erection when waking in the morning; nocturnal penile tumescence; morning glory; morning wood\nearly morning departure" },
	{ "question": "本番行為", "answers": [ "ほんばんこうい" ], "comment": "sexual intercourse (esp. with a prostitute); actual sex (in movies, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "本茶臼", "answers": [ "ほんちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "本駒掛け", "answers": [ "ほんこまがけ" ] },
	{ "question": "松葉崩し", "answers": [ "まつばくずし" ] },
	{ "question": "棒姉妹", "answers": [ "ぼうしまい" ] },
	{ "question": "椅子洗い", "answers": [ "いすあらい" ] },
	{ "question": "椋鳥", "answers": [ "むくどり" ], "comment": "grey starling (Sturnus cineraceus); gray starling; white-cheeked starling\nstarling (any bird of family Sturnidae)\nbumpkin; gullible person\nsixty-nine (sexual position)" },
	{ "question": "横笛", "answers": [ "よこぶえ" ], "comment": "transverse flute (e.g. a fife)" },
	{ "question": "機織り茶臼", "answers": [ "はたおりちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "櫓立ち", "answers": [ "やぐらだち" ] },
	{ "question": "欲求不満", "answers": [ "よっきゅうふまん" ], "comment": "frustration" },
	{ "question": "正室", "answers": [ "せいしつ" ], "comment": "legal wife (of a noble) (as opposed to a concubine)\nroom for receiving guests\nheir; successor" },
	{ "question": "正常位", "answers": [ "せいじょうい" ], "comment": "normal position (posture); missionary position" },
	{ "question": "母乳", "answers": [ "ぼにゅう" ], "comment": "mother's milk" },
	{ "question": "母娘丼", "answers": [ "おやこどん" ] },
	{ "question": "毛ジラミ", "answers": [ "けじらみ" ], "comment": "crab louse (Pthirus pubis); crab lice; pubic louse; pubic lice" },
	{ "question": "水揚げ", "answers": [ "みずあげ" ], "comment": "landing; unloading (e.g. a ship)\ncatch (of fish); takings\nsales (of a shop)\ndefloration (e.g. of a geisha)\npreservation (of cut flowers, in ikebana)" },
	{ "question": "泡姫", "answers": [ "あわひめ" ] },
	{ "question": "泡踊り", "answers": [ "あわおどり" ] },
	{ "question": "洞入り本手", "answers": [ "ほらいりほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "流産", "answers": [ "りゅうざん" ], "comment": "miscarriage; (spontaneous) abortion; abortive birth" },
	{ "question": "流鏑馬", "answers": [ "やぶさめ" ], "comment": "horseback archery" },
	{ "question": "浜千鳥", "answers": [ "はまちどり" ], "comment": "plover on the beach; plovers near the shore" },
	{ "question": "浣腸", "answers": [ "かんちょう" ], "comment": "(giving an) enema" },
	{ "question": "浮島本手", "answers": [ "うきしまほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "浮橋", "answers": [ "うきはし" ], "comment": "floating bridge; pontoon bridge" },
	{ "question": "浮気", "answers": [ "うわき" ], "comment": "extramarital sex; affair; fooling around\ninfidelity; wantonness; unfaithfulness; inconstancy; fickleness; caprice" },
	{ "question": "涎", "answers": [ "よだれ" ], "comment": "drool" },
	{ "question": "液体", "answers": [ "えきたい" ], "comment": "liquid; fluid" },
	{ "question": "淋病", "answers": [ "リンビョウ" ], "comment": "gonorrhea; gonorrhoea" },
	{ "question": "淫ら", "answers": [ "ミダラ" ], "comment": "obscene; indecent; lewd; bawdy; loose; improper; dirty" },
	{ "question": "淫乱", "answers": [ "いんらん" ], "comment": "debauched; lewd; lascivious; lecherous; salacious; wild" },
	{ "question": "淫行", "answers": [ "いんこう" ], "comment": "obscenity; harlotry" },
	{ "question": "淫靡", "answers": [ "いんび" ], "comment": "impurity; obscenity" },
	{ "question": "深山本手", "answers": [ "みやまほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "潮吹き", "answers": [ "しおふき" ], "comment": "spouting (e.g. of a whale, blowhole, etc.); blowing water\nMactra veneriformis (species of trough shell)\nfemale ejaculation; squirting" },
	{ "question": "濡れ場", "answers": [ "ぬれば" ], "comment": "(drama's) love scene" },
	{ "question": "濾胞", "answers": [ "ろほう" ], "comment": "follicle (esp. an ovarian follicle)" },
	{ "question": "煩悩", "answers": [ "ぼんのう" ], "comment": "worldly desires; evil passions; appetites of the flesh\nklesha (polluting thoughts such as greed, hatred and delusion, which result in suffering)" },
	{ "question": "熟女", "answers": [ "ジュクジョ" ], "comment": "attractive mature lady" },
	{ "question": "燕返し", "answers": [ "つばめがえし" ] },
	{ "question": "爆乳", "answers": [ "ばくにゅう" ], "comment": "enormous breasts" },
	{ "question": "牝", "answers": [ "めす" ], "comment": "female (animal)\nfemale; woman\nwife" },
	{ "question": "狂い獅子", "answers": [ "くるいじし" ] },
	{ "question": "猥褻", "answers": [ "わいせつ" ], "comment": "obscenity" },
	{ "question": "猥談", "answers": [ "ワイダン" ], "comment": "indecent talk" },
	{ "question": "猿轡", "answers": [ "さるぐつわ" ], "comment": "(mouth) gag" },
	{ "question": "獣姦", "answers": [ "じゅうかん" ], "comment": "bestiality; sodomy" },
	{ "question": "玉", "answers": [ "たま" ], "comment": "ball; sphere; globe; orb\nbead (of sweat, dew, etc.); drop; droplet\nball (in sports)\npile (of noodles, etc.)\nbullet\nbulb (i.e. a light bulb)\nlens (of glasses, etc.)\nbead (of an abacus)\nball (i.e. a testicle)\ngem; jewel (esp. spherical; sometimes used figuratively); pearl\nfemale entertainer (e.g. a geisha)\nperson (when commenting on their nature); character\nitem, funds or person used as part of a plot\negg\ncoin\nprecious; beautiful; excellent\nprecious stone (esp. jade)\negg (sometimes esp. as a sushi topping)\nstock or security being traded; product being bought or sold\nposition (in finance, the amount of a security either owned or owed by an investor or dealer)\ngeisha\ntime charge for a geisha\nking (of the junior player)" },
	{ "question": "理非知らず", "answers": [ "りひしらず" ] },
	{ "question": "生フェラ", "answers": [ "ナマフェラ" ] },
	{ "question": "生尺", "answers": [ "ナマシャク" ] },
	{ "question": "生殖器", "answers": [ "せいしょくき" ], "comment": "genital organ; genitalia; sexual organ; reproductive organ" },
	{ "question": "生理", "answers": [ "せいり" ], "comment": "physiology\nmenstruation; one's period; menses" },
	{ "question": "男娼", "answers": [ "だんしょう" ], "comment": "male prostitute" },
	{ "question": "男性器", "answers": [ "だんせいき" ], "comment": "male genitalia; male genital organs; penis" },
	{ "question": "男色", "answers": [ "だんしょく" ], "comment": "sodomy; male homosexuality" },
	{ "question": "異性愛", "answers": [ "いせいあい" ], "comment": "heterosexual love; heterosexuality" },
	{ "question": "痔", "answers": [ "じ" ], "comment": "hemorrhoids; piles" },
	{ "question": "痴女", "answers": [ "ちじょ" ], "comment": "female pervert" },
	{ "question": "痴漢", "answers": [ "ちかん" ], "comment": "masher; molester; pervert" },
	{ "question": "発情周期", "answers": [ "はつじょうしゅうき" ], "comment": "estrous cycle" },
	{ "question": "白光錦", "answers": [ "びゃっこうにしき" ] },
	{ "question": "百閉", "answers": [ "ひゃくへい" ] },
	{ "question": "盗撮", "answers": [ "とうさつ" ], "comment": "sneak photography; non-consensual photography; peeping photos" },
	{ "question": "相思相愛", "answers": [ "そうしそうあい" ], "comment": "mutual love" },
	{ "question": "真性包茎", "answers": [ "しんせいほうけい" ] },
	{ "question": "着床", "answers": [ "ちゃくしょう" ], "comment": "implantation (of an embryo)" },
	{ "question": "着衣セックス", "answers": [ "ちゃくいセックス" ] },
	{ "question": "睾丸", "answers": [ "こうがん" ], "comment": "testicles; testes; balls" },
	{ "question": "睾丸マッサージ", "answers": [ "こうがんまっさーじ" ] },
	{ "question": "砧", "answers": [ "きぬた" ], "comment": "wooden or stone block for beating cloth" },
	{ "question": "禁忌", "answers": [ "きんき" ], "comment": "taboo; day, time, direction, words, etc. that must be avoided\ncontraindication" },
	{ "question": "禁欲", "answers": [ "きんよく" ], "comment": "abstinence; self-control; celibacy; abnegation; ascetism" },
	{ "question": "稚児", "answers": [ "ちご" ], "comment": "(festivity) page\nbaby; child\nboys kept by pederasts\nbaby; child" },
	{ "question": "種付け", "answers": [ "たねつけ" ], "comment": "mating" },
	{ "question": "穴兄弟", "answers": [ "あなきょうだい" ], "comment": "men who have slept with the same woman; hole brothers" },
	{ "question": "穴開きパンツ", "answers": [ "あなあきぱんつ" ] },
	{ "question": "窒息プレイ", "answers": [ "ちっそくプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "窓の月", "answers": [ "まどのつき" ] },
	{ "question": "立ちバック", "answers": [ "たちバック" ] },
	{ "question": "立ち松葉", "answers": [ "たちまつば" ] },
	{ "question": "立ち花菱", "answers": [ "たちはなびし" ] },
	{ "question": "立ち鼎", "answers": [ "たちかなえ" ] },
	{ "question": "立位", "answers": [ "りつい" ], "comment": "standing position (working, sex, etc.); erect position; upright position" },
	{ "question": "童女", "answers": [ "どうじょ" ], "comment": "(little) girl" },
	{ "question": "童貞", "answers": [ "どうてい" ], "comment": "virginity (esp. of a man); male virgin\n(Catholic) nun" },
	{ "question": "竿姉妹", "answers": [ "さおしまい" ], "comment": "women who have slept with the same man" },
	{ "question": "第二次性徴", "answers": [ "だいにじせいちょう" ], "comment": "secondary sex characteristic" },
	{ "question": "笹舟本手", "answers": [ "ささぶねほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "筆下ろし", "answers": [ "ふでおろし" ], "comment": "using a new brush for the first time\ndoing something for the first time\nman losing his virginity (esp. to an older woman)" },
	{ "question": "筏崩し", "answers": [ "いかだくずし" ] },
	{ "question": "筏本手", "answers": [ "いかだほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "筏茶臼", "answers": [ "いかだちゃうす" ] },
	{ "question": "粘液", "answers": [ "ねんえき" ], "comment": "mucus; mucilage; viscous liquid; phlegm" },
	{ "question": "粘膜", "answers": [ "ねんまく" ], "comment": "mucous membrane" },
	{ "question": "精子", "answers": [ "せいし" ], "comment": "sperm" },
	{ "question": "精巣", "answers": [ "せいそう" ], "comment": "testicle" },
	{ "question": "精液", "answers": [ "せいえき" ], "comment": "semen" },
	{ "question": "精通", "answers": [ "せいつう" ], "comment": "acquaintance; having knowledge; being expert; being versed in; conversant\nfirst ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "精飲", "answers": [ "せいいん" ], "comment": "semen-drinking" },
	{ "question": "純潔", "answers": [ "じゅんけつ" ], "comment": "purity; chastity" },
	{ "question": "素人", "answers": [ "シロウト" ], "comment": "amateur; layman; ordinary person; novice\nrespectable woman (not a prostitute, hostess, geisha, etc.)\nunlicensed prostitute" },
	{ "question": "素股", "answers": [ "すまた" ], "comment": "bare thighs; inner thigh\nintercrural sex" },
	{ "question": "経口避妊薬", "answers": [ "けいこうひにんやく" ], "comment": "oral contraceptives; the pill" },
	{ "question": "絞り芙蓉", "answers": [ "しぼりふよう" ] },
	{ "question": "絶頂", "answers": [ "ぜっちょう" ], "comment": "top (of a mountain); summit\npeak; height; zenith; climax" },
	{ "question": "継室", "answers": [ "けいしつ" ], "comment": "second wife" },
	{ "question": "網代本手", "answers": [ "あじろほんて" ] },
	{ "question": "緊縛", "answers": [ "きんばく" ], "comment": "bind tightly\n(sexual) bondage" },
	{ "question": "縦筋", "answers": [ "たてすじ" ] },
	{ "question": "繁殖", "answers": [ "はんしょく" ], "comment": "breeding; multiplication; increase; propagation; reproduction" },
	{ "question": "美乳", "answers": [ "ビニュウ" ], "comment": "beautiful breasts; well-shaped breasts" },
	{ "question": "羞恥プレイ", "answers": [ "しゅうちプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "聖水", "answers": [ "せいすい" ], "comment": "holy water\nurine, especially as relates to urolagnia or urophilia" },
	{ "question": "肉体関係", "answers": [ "ニクタイカンケイ" ], "comment": "sexual relations; physical relations; carnal relations" },
	{ "question": "肉便器", "answers": [ "にくべんき" ], "comment": "promiscuous woman" },
	{ "question": "肉棒", "answers": [ "にくぼう" ], "comment": "dick; cock" },
	{ "question": "肛内射精", "answers": [ "こうないしゃせい" ] },
	{ "question": "股", "answers": [ "また" ], "comment": "crotch; crutch; groin; thigh\nfork (in a tree, road, river, etc.); tines (of a fork)\nthigh\nfemoral" },
	{ "question": "股間", "answers": [ "こかん" ], "comment": "nether region; between the legs; groin; crotch" },
	{ "question": "胎内", "answers": [ "たいない" ], "comment": "interior of the womb (of a pregnant woman); interior of the uterus\ninterior of a Buddhistic statue" },
	{ "question": "胚", "answers": [ "はい" ], "comment": "embryo; germ (e.g. wheat germ)" },
	{ "question": "胸ポチ", "answers": [ "むねポチ" ], "comment": "visible nipple (e.g. through clothing)" },
	{ "question": "脱毛", "answers": [ "だつもう" ], "comment": "hair loss\nhair removal; epilation; depilation" },
	{ "question": "腋", "answers": [ "わき" ], "comment": "armpit; under one's arm; side; flank\nbeside; close to; near; by\naside; to the side; away; out of the way\noff-track; off-topic\ndeuteragonist; supporting role\nsecond verse (in a linked series of poems)" },
	{ "question": "腋毛", "answers": [ "わきげ" ], "comment": "underarm hair" },
	{ "question": "腟", "answers": [ "ちつ" ], "comment": "vagina" },
	{ "question": "腟鏡", "answers": [ "ちつきょう" ] },
	{ "question": "腰", "answers": [ "こし" ], "comment": "back; lower back; waist; hips; lumbar region\nbody (of hair, noodle, paper, etc.); resilience; spring\nposture; position; pose; attitude" },
	{ "question": "腹上死", "answers": [ "ふくじょうし" ], "comment": "death during sexual intercourse" },
	{ "question": "膀胱", "answers": [ "ぼうこう" ], "comment": "urinary bladder" },
	{ "question": "膣", "answers": [ "ちつ" ], "comment": "vagina" },
	{ "question": "膣内射精", "answers": [ "ちつないしゃせい" ], "comment": "intravaginal ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "膣分泌液", "answers": [ "ちつぶんぴつえき" ], "comment": "vaginal secretion (during arousal); vaginal lubricant" },
	{ "question": "膣口", "answers": [ "ちつこう" ], "comment": "vaginal opening" },
	{ "question": "膣外射精", "answers": [ "ちつがいしゃせい" ], "comment": "extra-vaginal ejaculation" },
	{ "question": "膣鏡", "answers": [ "ちつきょう" ], "comment": "vaginal speculum; colposcope" },
	{ "question": "自慰", "answers": [ "じい" ], "comment": "masturbation; self consolation" },
	{ "question": "自涜", "answers": [ "じとく" ], "comment": "masturbation" },
	{ "question": "舌入れ", "answers": [ "シタイレ" ] },
	{ "question": "色欲", "answers": [ "しきよく" ], "comment": "lust; sexual appetite" },
	{ "question": "色町", "answers": [ "いろまち" ], "comment": "red-light district" },
	{ "question": "色里", "answers": [ "いろさと" ], "comment": "red-light district" },
	{ "question": "花菖蒲", "answers": [ "はなあやめ" ], "comment": "Japanese iris; blue flag; Iris ensata" },
	{ "question": "花菱責め", "answers": [ "はなびしぜめ" ] },
	{ "question": "花街", "answers": [ "かがい", "はなまち" ], "comment": "red-light district; prostitution quarter; geisha quarter" },
	{ "question": "若妻", "answers": [ "ワカヅマ" ] },
	{ "question": "菊", "answers": [ "キク" ], "comment": "chrysanthemum (Chrysanthemum morifolium)" },
	{ "question": "菊一文字", "answers": [ "きくいちもんじ" ] },
	{ "question": "萌え", "answers": [ "もえ" ], "comment": "sprouting; budding\ncrush (anime, manga term); fascination; infatuation" },
	{ "question": "虚乳", "answers": [ "キョニュウ" ] },
	{ "question": "虹の架け橋", "answers": [ "にじのかけはし" ] },
	{ "question": "衆道", "answers": [ "しゅどう" ], "comment": "male homosexuality; pederasty" },
	{ "question": "裏ビデオ", "answers": [ "うらビデオ" ] },
	{ "question": "裏筋", "answers": [ "ウラスジ" ], "comment": "frenulum of prepuce of penis" },
	{ "question": "裸", "answers": [ "はだか" ], "comment": "naked; nude; bare" },
	{ "question": "裸体", "answers": [ "らたい" ], "comment": "naked body; nudity" },
	{ "question": "裾野", "answers": [ "すその" ], "comment": "foot of a mountain; plain at the foot of a mountain\nrange; spread; extent; encompassing circle" },
	{ "question": "襞", "answers": [ "ひだ" ], "comment": "pleats; creases; gills of a mushroom (mycology)" },
	{ "question": "西川口", "answers": [ "ニシカワグチ" ] },
	{ "question": "視姦", "answers": [ "しかん" ], "comment": "ogling; eyeing (lecherously); leering; staring" },
	{ "question": "触り放題", "answers": [ "サワリホウダイ" ] },
	{ "question": "言葉責め", "answers": [ "コトバゼメ" ], "comment": "verbal abuse" },
	{ "question": "調教", "answers": [ "チョウキョウ" ], "comment": "training (animals); breaking (animals)" },
	{ "question": "豆", "answers": [ "まめ" ], "comment": "legume (esp. edible legumes or their seeds, such as beans, peas, pulses, etc.); beans; peas\nsoya bean (Glycine max); soybean; soy\nfemale genitalia (esp. the clitoris)\nkidney\nminiature; tiny\nchild" },
	{ "question": "貝合わせ", "answers": [ "かいあわせ" ], "comment": "shell-matching game popular with court aristocrats during the Heian period\ntribadism" },
	{ "question": "貞操帯", "answers": [ "ていそうたい" ], "comment": "chastity belt" },
	{ "question": "貧乳", "answers": [ "ひんにゅう" ], "comment": "tiny breasts" },
	{ "question": "超根", "answers": [ "チョウコン" ] },
	{ "question": "足コキ", "answers": [ "あしこき" ], "comment": "footjob" },
	{ "question": "身掻き", "answers": [ "みみかき" ] },
	{ "question": "輪姦", "answers": [ "りんかん" ], "comment": "gang rape" },
	{ "question": "輸卵管", "answers": [ "ゆらんかん" ], "comment": "oviduct; Fallopian tubes" },
	{ "question": "近親相姦", "answers": [ "きんしんそうかん" ], "comment": "incest" },
	{ "question": "逆アナル舐め", "answers": [ "ぎゃくあなるなめ" ] },
	{ "question": "逆レイプ", "answers": [ "ぎゃくれいぷ" ], "comment": "reverse rape; sexual assault by a female of a male" },
	{ "question": "通常位", "answers": [ "つうじょうい" ] },
	{ "question": "逢引", "answers": [ "あいびき" ], "comment": "(secret) date; clandestine meeting; assignation; tryst; rendezvous" },
	{ "question": "逢瀬", "answers": [ "おうせ" ], "comment": "rendezvous; tryst; (lover's) meeting; (secret) date" },
	{ "question": "遅漏", "answers": [ "ちろう" ], "comment": "late ejaculation; impotence" },
	{ "question": "遅番", "answers": [ "オソバン" ], "comment": "the late shift" },
	{ "question": "遊女", "answers": [ "ゆうじょ" ], "comment": "prostitute; harlot" },
	{ "question": "遊廓", "answers": [ "ゆうかく" ], "comment": "red light district" },
	{ "question": "遊里", "answers": [ "ゆうり" ], "comment": "red light district" },
	{ "question": "遺精", "answers": [ "いせい" ], "comment": "nocturnal emissions (of semen); oneirogmus" },
	{ "question": "避妊具", "answers": [ "ひにんぐ" ], "comment": "contraceptive device; birth-control device" },
	{ "question": "金玉", "answers": [ "きんたま" ], "comment": "testicles\ngold and jewels; precious object" },
	{ "question": "金蹴りプレイ", "answers": [ "きんけりぷれい" ] },
	{ "question": "釣瓶落とし", "answers": [ "つるべおとし" ], "comment": "sinking quickly" },
	{ "question": "閨", "answers": [ "ねや" ], "comment": "sleeping quarters; bedroom (mainly refers to one used by a married couple)\ninner room; inner sanctum" },
	{ "question": "陰嚢", "answers": [ "いんのう" ], "comment": "scrotum; testicles; scrotal\npinecone; pine cone" },
	{ "question": "陰核", "answers": [ "いんかく" ], "comment": "clitoris\ntesticles\npenis" },
	{ "question": "陰核亀頭", "answers": [ "いんかくきとう" ], "comment": "glans clitoridis" },
	{ "question": "陰梃", "answers": [ "いんてい" ] },
	{ "question": "陰毛", "answers": [ "いんもう" ], "comment": "pubic hair" },
	{ "question": "陰茎", "answers": [ "いんけい" ], "comment": "penis" },
	{ "question": "陰裂", "answers": [ "いんれつ" ], "comment": "pudendal cleft; rima pudendi" },
	{ "question": "陰部", "answers": [ "いんぶ" ], "comment": "the genital area" },
	{ "question": "陰門", "answers": [ "いんもん" ], "comment": "(female) genitalia; vulva" },
	{ "question": "陰間", "answers": [ "かげま" ], "comment": "homosexual prostitute who sold favors at banquets, etc. (late Edo)\nactor-in-training in kabuki" },
	{ "question": "陽物", "answers": [ "ようぶつ" ], "comment": "phallus; penis" },
	{ "question": "隠語", "answers": [ "いんご" ], "comment": "secret language; jargon; cant\nhumbug" },
	{ "question": "雁が首", "answers": [ "かりがくび" ] },
	{ "question": "雄", "answers": [ "オス" ], "comment": "male (animal)\nmale; man\nhusband" },
	{ "question": "雄性", "answers": [ "ゆうせい" ], "comment": "male characteristics; manliness" },
	{ "question": "雌", "answers": [ "メス" ], "comment": "female (animal)\nfemale; woman\nwife" },
	{ "question": "雌性", "answers": [ "しせい" ], "comment": "female" },
	{ "question": "雑食", "answers": [ "ザッショク" ], "comment": "omnivorous" },
	{ "question": "露出プレイ", "answers": [ "ろしゅつプレイ" ] },
	{ "question": "露出狂", "answers": [ "ろしゅつきょう" ], "comment": "exhibitionist; flasher" },
	{ "question": "青姦", "answers": [ "あおかん" ], "comment": "sleeping under the stars\nhaving sex outdoors" },
	{ "question": "鞭", "answers": [ "むち" ], "comment": "whip; lash; scourge\nstick; cane; rod; pointer" },
	{ "question": "顔出しＮＧ", "answers": [ "かおだしえぬじー" ] },
	{ "question": "顔射", "answers": [ "がんしゃ" ], "comment": "ejaculation onto partner's face" },
	{ "question": "顔面騎乗", "answers": [ "がんめんきじょう" ], "comment": "facesitting (sex act)" },
	{ "question": "風俗嬢", "answers": [ "ふうぞくじょう" ], "comment": "woman who works in the sex industry" },
	{ "question": "飲尿", "answers": [ "いんにょう" ] },
	{ "question": "飲精", "answers": [ "いんせい" ] },
	{ "question": "首引き恋慕", "answers": [ "くびひきれんぼ" ] },
	{ "question": "首輪", "answers": [ "くびわ" ], "comment": "(animal) collar\nnecklace; choker" },
	{ "question": "騎乗位", "answers": [ "きじょうい" ], "comment": "sexual position where the man lies flat on his back and the woman sits on top; cowgirl position" },
	{ "question": "骨盤", "answers": [ "こつばん" ], "comment": "pelvis" },
	{ "question": "鬼畜", "answers": [ "きちく" ], "comment": "brute; savage; fiend" },
	{ "question": "魔羅", "answers": [ "まら" ], "comment": "obstacle to Buddhist practice\npenis" },
	{ "question": "鯉の滝登り", "answers": [ "コイノタキノボリ" ] },
	{ "question": "鳴き", "answers": [ "ナキ" ] },
	{ "question": "鳴門後ろ取り", "answers": [ "なるとうしろどり" ] },
	{ "question": "黄金", "answers": [ "オウゴン" ], "comment": "gold" },
	{ "question": "経膣", "answers": [ "けいちつ" ], "comment": "transvaginal" },
	{ "question": "膣内", "answers": [ "ちつない" ], "comment": "【１級】\nintravaginal" },
	{ "question": "膣口", "answers": [ "ちつこう" ], "comment": "【１級】\nvaginal opening" },
	{ "question": "膣壁", "answers": [ "ちつへき" ], "comment": "【１級】\nvaginal wall" },
	{ "question": "膣錠", "answers": [ "ちつじょう" ], "comment": "【１級】" },
	{ "question": "鼻フェラ", "answers": [ "はなふぇら" ] }
]
}
